It's not a dream, right?
This is the real you, right?
Of course it's me.
Thanks for waking me up.
And thank you too, Kuroi.
You're not hurt or anything, are you?
No, I'm okay.
What about you?
Are you feeling okay?
Show me your soul, Jim, and I can...
Would you stop worrying? I'm fine.
Look it, I'm better than ever, and it's all thanks to you.
Where are we?
I don't recognize this place.
We're in a rumor called the Eternal Sakura, I think.
The Eternal Sakura?
It's not in the rumor files I've seen.
It seems this tree is its core.
I think I've heard that name before.
Somewhere.
Now what?
It's the Labyrinth!
I'll be waiting for you, Irohata Maki.
I'll wait right here until the day you and the other three come to visit me.
I'll wait as long as it takes.
Even if all the stories end, I'll be waiting.
It's the Alley, right where we entered.
It seems that Uasa escaped.
It's the Labyrinth
It smells like that.
But...
The Universal cinema is not overwSo..
It's like us?
It feels like nine o'clock would hurt.
It feels like the first one landed.
The Labyrinth has been الذ standing on o'clock and pressed..
It feels like everything at all.
It feels like us didn'tose the alarm.
I don't fall like you guys for the suit as we were a boy!
It feels like we're up at our team.
It feels like you say Kadesi, so that The Lad garder is a sophomore.
So you can't 8th according to Doh, where the Lord importantly needs to get you down.
We're home!
It's usually way cleaner than this!
Yachiyo's kind of a stickler about tidiness.
Really?
Yes, but I've been busy lately.
Where are all the other girls?
Yeah, Yachiyo. Where are they?
I don't know.
I saw them last at the Memory Museum.
The Magius probably has them now.
Oh no!
How about you? You're a black feather. You must know something.
If you're talking about the girls in Iroha's dream, I don't.
I've never seen them around Magius' headquarters before.
Hold on a second! You mean you're in the wings of the Magius?!
Uh, yeah, sort of.
She was sent to hunt you down, Iroha.
By one of her leaders. A girl named Nemu Hiragi.
No way! Really?
I wasn't hunting you. Nemu wanted me to find you and bring you back to her is all.
Wait, then you spoke to her? So is she doing okay? Is she?
Uh...
I haven't seen her in forever and I'm worried about her.
I'm sorry, but...
She told me she's dying.
What are you talking about? Nemu's dying? For real? I-I'm sorry.
Nemu is the one making all the rumors. As for Toka, she's the one who makes the doppels.
You need to tell us what the Magius are planning. Does it have something to do with Nemu's condition?
I really don't know anything. I just do what I'm told, that's all.
All right, then. I believe you, but you have to take me to see them right away!
We were all friends. The best of friends. We were always together and always had fun.
I remember how sweet and cheerful they were. They were like my special little sisters.
But when I saw Toka again, she didn't remember me at all.
I think that if Nemu remembers me, maybe we can get some answers out of her.
We can find out what the Magius are really up to. And maybe we can even save Nemu's life!
I don't know.
Iroha, I know how you must feel. But you hurt her. Nemu wanted to capture you.
That's right, and I want to find out why.
I don't know why I lost touch with her and Toka.
Or what happened to my friends from the villa while I was asleep.
Or why I was asleep.
I can't just sit here and do nothing.
All I want is to get some answers.
All right, then.
Let's go find our roommates and Nemu and Toka.
Kuroi,
take us to your HQ, to Hotel Fent Hope.
Now.
The massive typhoon that formed in the Southern Seas absorbed several other typhoons
and is heading north.
The weather bureau warns that it will reach landfall soon, so be prepared to evacuate.
The thing about Hotel Fent Hope is it's constantly moving, so the door's always in a different spot.
It looks like that trellis of Chinese cucumber is where the door is now.
So how do we get inside?
We have to use this thing.
Wait, I didn't do that.
The Omanes.
Oh my gosh.
What are you people doing here?
Only members of Magia's know about the store.
Aha!
That Black Feather Rookie betrayed us!
What?
No, I didn't.
One of the Magia's sent me out on a mission to bring...
To bring Yachiyo Nanami in for a visit?
I don't think so.
He didn't have a choice.
Hurry!
Okay!
That does it, Yachiyo.
This is the last time you're going to interfere with us!
We're going to get you back for all the times you stuck your nose in our plans.
Come on, then.
So this is Hotel Fent help.
Yeah, sort of.
We ended up in the basement level, actually.
Really?
Those white feathers we ran into must have exited through here.
Can you hear me, Yachiyo?
Yachiyo?
Oh great, the portal's closed.
I hope Yachiyo's okay.
I'm sure she's doing just fine.
She can handle those too.
I hope so.
Will this train take us to the main part of the hotel?
It'll get us closer to it.
Before you said, Nemu told you to come find me.
Mm-hmm.
Did she look sick?
I couldn't tell.
Oh.
I'm curious.
What made you decide to join the wings of the Magius?
There weren't many witches left in my town.
And when I came here for grief seeds, the witches were too strong for me.
But you didn't have to join the Magius.
Other magical girls would have helped you.
Yeah, maybe.
But I've used my doppel a bunch, so...
What?
That's bad for you!
Yeah, but without it, I'd be a witch now.
It's the same with you, isn't it?
I guess so.
But I almost lost control of my doppel.
That was too close.
Well, I say we stop using them.
We don't need to rely on our doppels if we don't want to.
If we all work together, we can do anything!
I don't think it's as easy as all that.
I'd feel terrible if someone ended up dying for my sake.
All I'm saying is, you have friends now.
You don't need the Magius' help.
Anyway, you're not alone in this city.
Hey, do you know if any other magical girls from Takarazaki came here before you?
Are you okay?
What would you do if all the magical girls that came to Kamehama
came because they were so weak they couldn't survive on their own?
That's easy. I'd help them out.
Someone helped me when I needed it.
I don't remember what's up ahead here, so be careful.
It's Rana!
Iroha!
Where have you been? We were worried sick!
Oh, um...
I got stuck in something.
I was worried about you guys, too.
Does that cloak mean you...
Yeah.
I joined the wings of the Magius.
I'm a black feather.
At least I used to be.
Huh?
We ran out on them.
It's safe!
Kaire!
What happened? Are you hurt?
No, and her Soul Gem's fine, too.
She's sick of this place and these people.
She'll feel better once we get her out of here.
On second thought, maybe we should go back.
What? Have you lost your mind?
I didn't come all this way just to...
I don't feel right about this.
If we went back and talked to everyone, that won't work.
This is all my fault.
I should have done what the coordinator said to do.
Whatever.
We're getting out. Come on.
No! Wait!
For what? We need to leave now.
When we got to the entrance, the Amane sisters suddenly showed up.
They closed the portal.
There's white feathers up ahead?
Why didn't you say so?
That I just did!
Sorry I snapped.
But we can't stand around talking.
We're being followed.
We'll have to take the long way back to Fent Hope and find another way out.
Do you know where you're going?
Yeah, of course I do.
Don't I, Kaire?
Yeah.
R-Rena!
I think you should let a coordinator check her out.
No way!
Stay together.
Huh?
We keep hitting dead ends.
The Magical Girls here won't tell us anything about the Magius.
And none of the ones we talked to so far seem to know anything about Mommy either.
By the look of these flyers, the Magius are actively recruiting Magical Girls.
So why are they avoiding us?
It's like banging our heads against a wall.
I know.
I hope Mommy's okay.
We all do.
At least we're not walking around in a cave anymore.
Where are you going?
Stop!
Iroha?
Huh?
What is all this?
No way!
They're all filled with...
Witches!
This is where the Magius raise them.
They can raise witches?
Yeah.
They call this place their witch farm.
They catch a witch, bring it here, and raise it by feeding it human emotions.
Is that what the rumors are for?
To catch people so they can get food for witches?
Yeah, that's how it works.
Why would they do this?
To get their gravestites, I guess.
I mean, why else would they do something so crazy?
That's cruel!
Sure, they're witches now, but at one point they were magical girls like us!
Yeah, I know.
It sucks, but we need to focus on getting out.
Doesn't that scare you?
Ending up like them?
No.
Not even a little?
It makes me sad.
No one deserves this fate.
To become a witch, then get locked up in a cage and forced to wait to be turned into a grief seat?
It's not right!
I can't imagine how that feels.
What is that?
It's not a witch!
It's an Uasa!
Shh!
Watch out!
This was a guard!
I felt like
It's a ghost
It's not a witch
It's a just sort of beam
It's a suspect
Bop!
This is a witch
It's a witch
And she says
It is a witch
She says
It's a witch
My soul gem.
Oh no.
If I'm gonna die...
No!
What are you doing?
You were going to use your dapper, weren't you?
I didn't have a choice.
You do!
Connect with me.
Okay.
Here we go!
We did it!
That was great!
Our powers made a great combo!
We make a great team!
You think?
That was the best connect I ever did.
And you made it happen!
Wasn't that awesome, Rena?
Ah!
Kai!
Oh no.
Kai, wake up!
Please!
Rena...
I'm sorry.
Kait我就...
Katie!
Randy!
Rana!
Her doppel's out of control!
Why here? Why now?
It's cause she used her doppel too much!
Kurue! We could try cutting her loose like Yachiyo did with me!
No. It's fused too much with her.
I can't tell where it's safe for us to attack!
What do we do?
Be careful! It's trying to smash everything!
Rana! I need your help to stop her!
Won't we kill her if we attack her?
Don't worry! You've always been there to save her!
And this time isn't any different!
You're right! Saving her is what I do best!
Curly!
Come on it!
Don't let my power go to waste!
I won't!
Haidei! Haidei!
What did I tell you ladies?
If you don't get regular checkups with me, bad things will happen!
Mitama! Momoko!
She'll be okay now, right?
Haidei!
There! We're all done now!
W-what do you mean done?
Kaidei!
What the hell's going on here?!
This is where we keep overdoses!
If you use your doppel too much, it goes out of control and takes you over!
The patients you see here are all magical girls that happen too!
Why didn't you tell us about this?!
Actually, I did say there'd be side effects from overuse!
You didn't say this was a side effect!
I warned you though, that should have been enough!
So now what? Are you gonna keep her locked up like this forever?
She's not a prisoner!
I'm keeping her isolated until she can get treatment!
That's all!
When will she turn back the way she used to be?!
Good question!
I suppose she will after the Magius achieves their goal!
What do you mean, you suppose?!
Will she or won't she?!
I have no idea!
No one's tried changing them back yet!
It might work, it might not!
I'm sorry, but that's how it is!
What kind of answer is that supposed to be?!
Do the Magius save magical girls or not?!
I'm sorry, that's how it is!
And you're okay with that?!
Mitama...
If this is part of the Magius' plan...
You have to admit it's not right!
It might not seem right to you...
But if I let them out, they'd cause all sorts of trouble!
Think about it!
They might be stuck in here, but at least they're alive!
Alive?! Like this?!
It's the same as being a witch!
This shouldn't happen to us!
Oh...
Look at all of them!
Do you think they're dreaming?
Dreaming?
When I'm asleep, I keep having this nightmare...
Everyone was suffering and turning into witches...
Over and over and over...
But when my doppel took control, the dreams I had were so peaceful...
There were no nightmares in that world...
If you're faced with something as scary as our fate...
I can understand why someone would choose to do the wrong thing to escape it...
I guess so...
Once I talk to Nemu, I'll find out the point of all this...
She's like my little sister...
I can help her!
What do you think you can help her with?
Remember when you found out the truth about us magical girls?
It scared you!
Nemu's suffering just like us, and I want to be there for her...
For support...
Same with everyone...
I have to let them know they're not alone, and that there's hope!
It's almost time to start...
One last battle and magical girls everywhere will be free and safe and happy...